# leandrocitygear $\circ$ leandrocitygear $\circ$

## Leandro De la cruz

Software Engineer

1 year of experience

leandrocitygear@icloud.com

Portfolio: leandrodelacruz.netlify.app/

I'm a Software Engineer Based in San Juan, Puerto Rico. For me Software is all about Simplicity and Precision. Software must be worthy of its users.

Seeking a software engineering role that allows me to utilize my innovative mindset, and problem-solving skills to help a company achieve its software development objectives.

Skills: JavaScript 1 year · Intermediate React 1 year · Intermediate Node.js 1 year · Beginner HTML 1 year · Advanced

(CSS 1 year · Advanced Redux 1 year · Beginner Electron.js 1 year · Beginner)

### Experience

**DoorDash** Jul 2021 to Jun 2024

Delivery Driver San Juan, PR

Gym en la Universidad del Sagrado Corazon

Aug 2019 to May 2021

Front Desk Assistant and Equipment maintenance San Juan, PR

Oficina de Admisiones en la Universidad del Sagrado Corazon

Assistant San Juan, PR

Aug 2018 to May 2019

Aug 2016 to Dec 2021

#### Education

Universidad Del Sagrado Corazon

Bachelor's degree, Communication and Media Studies

CodeCademy Jul 2023

Certification, Front-End Engineer

#### Languages

Spanish Fluent

English Fluent